‎SPORTS FESTIVAL
‎MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL
‎THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL
‎6:30 A.M.
‎What's up, Tsukko?
‎Oh, nothing, really...
‎It's just I'm only on the cheer squad
‎because I went with the herd mentality.
‎Now I'm feeling nervous,
‎and worrying about messing up my moves.
‎I'm more of a culture kid than sports.
‎I'm a little worried about whether people
‎would even want me rooting for them.
‎Of course they want you rooting for them!
‎So you better get out there and cheer.
‎I know how you feel.
‎Will you please root for Momoka?
‎She wants me to root for her.
‎Well, it's not like Momoka's
‎a bad person or anything,
‎and it's not like I want
‎anything more from Amamiya.
‎In fact, Amamiya's nice to everyone.
‎So of course it makes sense
‎that he's nice to me too.
‎And it's not like anybody
‎really cares about my feelings.
‎So there's no big deal...
‎Don't overthink this.
‎Act normal.
‎EPISODE 13
‎PERCEPTION
‎THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL 7:00 A.M.
‎FINAL MORNING PRACTICE
‎-Let's win this thing!
‎-Yeah!
‎8:00 A.M. - THE GIRLS DO THEIR HAIR
‎I've got plenty of blue accessories here.
‎Come take whatever you want for your hair.
‎THOSE WITH TIME TO SPARE
‎BECAUSE THEY HAVE SHORT HAIR
‎-Yota. Can I go all out with your hair?
‎-All out?
‎You sure this is okay?
‎It's not gonna look strange?
‎It's fine!
‎Everyone's hair looks amazing.
‎And the girls too.
‎20 MINS AGO - NICE SOFT HAIR
‎FRIENDLY STRANGER SENIORS
‎Let me do your hair.
‎Koyun, this is amazing.
‎They called it "onion hair."
‎-‎Stop that, Hino!
‎-Onions?
‎Amamiya's just over--
‎Oh, man. You see?
‎Miki, what face is that supposed to be?
‎SNAP
‎You look good.
‎What?
‎You all do.
‎SPORTS FESTIVAL
‎MORNING EDITION
‎Go, Yota! Minato!
‎Nope! Too high up! This is legit scary!
‎She looks cute. Like a hamster.
‎So cute!
‎OBSTACLE COURSE
‎SWIFT
‎Koyun, you're so fast!
‎What kind of running is that?
‎GIRL'S TUG-OF-WAR
‎Yeah!
‎Miki! I've never seen you shine
‎more than you do today!
‎ALL-IN RELAY (FIRST YEARS)
‎STEP STEP
‎I am a disgrace...
‎You're fine.
‎CLUB VS CLUB RELAY
‎Minato, what are you doing?
‎That's not like you.
‎Ready for a picture?
‎These outfits are poppin'!
‎Definitely.
‎The pants Miki made for me fit perfectly.
‎Wow! All the seniors look great.
‎Momoka?
‎You look so good in your outfit.
‎You too, Momoka.
‎Don't often see you in an up-do.
‎The third years did it up for me.
‎-Very nice.
‎-‎What's this?
‎-You look nice too.
‎-Thanks.
‎Since when were Miki and Momoka so close?
‎And Tsukiko. You look very cute too.
‎What? What?
‎No, how could I ever compare to you...
‎WARM WARM
‎-You look like a critter. Very cute!
‎-‎What do I do?
‎WHOOSH
‎I forgot something in my locker.
‎Want me to come with?
‎I'm fine.
‎I can't do this. What do I do?
‎What do I do with this disgusting feeling?
‎WHOMP
‎CATCH
‎Koyun?
‎Why do we always
‎seem to bump into each other?
‎I apologize for my lack of due caution.
‎LIFT
‎There you are, Yota. Hayato's over--
‎BANG - WHOA
‎No, it's not--
‎Then what is it?
‎What do I do?
‎I...
‎RUN
‎I'm going back to Miki and the others.
‎PANT PANT
‎What am I doing?
‎Koyun?
‎AFTERNOON
‎CHEER COMPETITION
‎ALL GROUPS SUCCESSFULLY FINISHED
‎TIME FOR PHOTOS
‎(WHILE POINTS ARE TALLIED)
‎FIRST YEARS
‎Thank you so much!
‎He's so good-looking.
‎What a great quality photo.
‎AHAHAHA
‎CHATTER CHATTER
‎I'm gonna print this
‎as a poster for my room.
‎I just gained 100 years of life.
‎To be young again.
‎Shall I get a photo?
‎No, I couldn't.
‎Hello, Amamiya.
‎Can we get a photo together?
‎Yeah, sure.
‎Of course.
‎All you have to do is ask.
‎But I'm too scared to do that right now.
‎I lost everyone.
‎Maybe they've all gone back
‎to the changing rooms?
‎BA-BUMP
‎Koyun!
‎HOP HOP
‎SHE'S CALLING ME...
‎Come get in our photo, Koyun.
‎TROT TROT
‎I hope that's not what she wants.
‎I'd feel like a third wheel.
‎Sorry to trouble you.
‎Could you take our picture for us, please?
‎Sure.
‎Um...
‎What is that face supposed to mean?
‎Thank you. Now, shall we get one together?
‎SWOOSH - CLICK
‎SWOOSH
‎Thank you! And see you!
‎EYES HALF CLOSED &
‎MOUTH HALF OPEN
‎I must look awful in that photo.
‎Let's get a photo over there.
‎Come on. Let's go.
‎-Photos.
‎Can we get a picture?
‎I could ask him...
‎-‎This is our only chance.
‎BA-BUMP
‎OUT OF CHARACTER - IS IT GROSS?
‎I'm searching for reasons not to ask.
‎DON'T EVEN LIKE PHOTOS
‎WILL I GIVE AWAY MY CRUSH?
‎IT'S UNNATURAL - WILL I SCARE HER?
‎All these negative thoughts.
‎Hmm...
‎You two. Stand right there.
‎Okay. We made a memory.
‎Now, Minato. The soccer club's waiting.
‎-Say goodbye.
‎-Hey, wait!
‎Wait a minute! Let me get a better photo.
‎I hate candid shots.
‎What a pain.
‎Got any cool poses?
‎Well...
‎FLUSTER FLUSTER
‎PUNCH
‎-Hey.
‎-Here I go.
‎Minato!
‎Kenta's calling for you.
‎Coming!
‎PLONK
‎Do you think the soccer club
‎is always so casual with its members?
‎Hey, Koyun.
‎Is there something you're hiding from me?
‎SMIRK
‎DISAPPEAR
‎Hey.
‎No. I'm not hiding anything from you.
‎You really can be quite distant, Koyun.
‎-BIRTHDAY? YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD US
‎-WAS I SUPPOSED TO?
‎Like how you kept your birthday from us.
‎-It makes me kind of sad.
‎-‎Soot, soot.
‎LOOK
‎It's not that I'm hiding it, it's just...
‎I only just noticed it myself recently.
‎Okay.
‎I thought it could be
‎just me imagining things.
‎I don't know it for certain yet.
‎Okay.
‎So I didn't think it was worth
‎mentioning to others yet.
‎If it's something churning around inside
‎that you can't seem to set straight,
‎maybe letting it out
‎might help you feel better?
‎You definitely helped me feel better.
‎Yota.
‎CREEP CREEP
‎OPEN - RATTLE
‎COME HERE
‎CREEP CREEP
‎LOOK LOOK
‎So, I...
‎I see.
‎Koyun. You have the worst taste.
‎He says that, but he looks happy enough.
‎I get it now.
‎We both feel the same way.
‎If I'm being really truly honest...
‎At first, I felt awkward around him.
‎You could say I was almost scared of him.
‎That's how it started.
‎But why?
‎How did I not notice
‎my feelings had changed?
‎I mean, I can't explain why,
‎or what even this is, but...
‎That's just how it is.
‎Shall I work on getting you two alone?
‎Do not do that!
‎SHE DOES IT
‎I'm so sorry.
‎HAHA
‎I... I don't want to take things
‎any further than friends.
‎MATSURI - ONDO NO MASTER
‎I'm just happy for us to hang out together
‎and to get along as friends.
‎I feel like that's all I need.
‎Where we are right now
‎feels the most comfortable.
‎I don't want to ruin that.
‎You're just like me.
‎Is my heart gonna be
‎covered in soot soon too?
‎Welcome to the club.
‎I don't want this.
‎All points have been tallied.
‎Please come to the school courtyard
‎for the closing ceremony.
‎But this is Minato we're talking about.
‎This is gonna be tough.
‎Yeah, I can imagine.
‎FOUND YOU!
‎Koyun! Yota! There you are.
‎Perfect! We found you just in time.
‎We still don't have a photo
‎with all four of us.
‎What do I do?
‎Now I'm overly self-conscious because
‎we were literally just talking about it.
‎Were Yota and Koyun alone just now?
‎They were together all this time?
‎LOOK
‎BUMP
‎Don't you look at me.
‎BONK
‎Same goes for you.
‎HEH
‎AGAPE
‎Where we are right now
‎feels the most comfortable.
‎I don't want to ruin that.
‎I want to keep it...
‎Ready?
‎PUSH
‎Get closer.
‎CLICK
‎I really hope things can stay
‎as peaceful as they are right now.
‎GRADE 2 CLASS 2
‎AFTER HOMEROOM
‎This year's sports festival
‎was so much more fun than last year's.
‎I feel the same.
‎CHATTER CHATTER
‎I was nervous about cheering,
‎but once I got into it, I had fun.
‎Agreed.
‎LAST YEAR'S SPORTS FESTIVAL
‎CLASS WITH ZERO SOLIDARITY
‎I guess these things
‎depend on who you do it with.
‎I was just thinking that,
‎but you didn't have to say it out loud.
‎By the way, where's Miki?
‎GRADE 2 CLASS 2
‎ON THE PE COMMITTEE
‎She's on clean-up duty.
‎HEH HEH
‎Good luck, Yota.
‎All right! Let's go do karaoke!
‎HERE FOR SOME REASON
‎-I'm starving.
‎-I'm gonna order a mountain of fries.
‎-Yeah!
‎-Yay!
‎Shall we wait for Yota?
‎-I'll shoot him a message.
‎-Okay.
‎The guys seem in good spirits.
‎They sure do.
‎PLONK
‎-Can I help you?
‎-You looked at me.
‎Are you guys waiting for Miki?
‎No. We were just about to head home.
‎She told us to go on without her.
‎I see.
‎Well then, Amamiya. I'll see you later.
‎Let's go, Tsukiko.
‎Really, Koyuki? Just like that?
‎Amamiya probably wanted to talk to you.
‎Then again, I'm not going to stop you.
‎I'll send you the photo
‎we took today later, okay?
‎SHE'S GOING TO GET IN TOUCH LATER
‎Lucky you, Amamiya!
‎Hey, wait!
‎The wrap party on Saturday.
‎Are you coming?
‎What party?
‎The wrap party for the cheer squad.
‎We're going out for yakiniku.
‎-Since when?
‎We literally just got a text message
‎requesting attendance for the blue group.
‎Hey, you're right.
‎I turned off notifications,
‎so I didn't hear it.
‎Same.
‎Why would you turn off notifications?
‎-Too many people.
‎BLUE GROUP - ENDLESS RESPONSE
‎GOT IT - OK - ALL RIGHT - YES
‎HANG
‎Hey, Amamiya. What are you up to now?
‎And here you are again.
‎In my class. As usual.
‎Hey, what's going on?
‎The wrap party.
‎You coming?
‎Well...
‎I dunno, I have work on Saturday, so...
‎What time?
‎From 11:00 till 3:00.
‎We're meeting at 6:00.
‎That's plenty of time.
‎You're not coming, Hikawa?
‎Why not? We all need to be there.
‎You're one to talk.
‎Come on! Let's go.
‎Shimojima's not coming either?
‎Now I'm sad.
‎UM...
‎We're all the ones from Class 2, right?
‎LOOKY LOOKY
‎NOD
‎Okay. We'll come.
‎-See you.
‎See you tomorrow.
‎They just had a whole
‎conversation without words.
‎SATURDAY
‎Girls scare me like that, man.
‎My heart's pounding.
‎We agreed to go!
‎We did.
‎I can already see myself hiding
‎in a corner struggling to keep up.
‎What do I do?
‎Let me sit with you.
‎SUPPLIES
‎SCAVENGER HUNT
‎Man, the sports festival
‎was over in a flash.
‎It sure was.
‎I'm already sad thinking we won't
‎get to practice cheering anymore.
‎-But I'm excited for the wrap party.
‎-Me too.
‎SUPPLIES ROOM
‎Sure, there's the wrap party, but we four
‎have gotta hang out again soon.
‎Where shall we go next?
‎Maybe back to Uppi for round two?
‎They might have different events on
‎for different seasons in the year.
‎UPPI
‎We could see Uppi in all four seasons.
‎I'd like to see that. That's a great idea.
‎But just putting it out there,
‎I haven't forgotten about our promise
‎to hang out just the two of us.
‎You'd better not forget either.
‎I would never--
‎Let's do it all!
‎Miki!
‎Ouch...
‎Yota, are you all right?
‎Sorry! No, I mean-- Something fell.
‎I get it.
‎Thank you, Yota.
‎You bumped your forehead. Are you okay?
‎I'm fine.
‎Hold up.
‎You're acting like a little boy
‎embarrassed by girls.
‎Cut that out, bro. It's just me.
‎It's not about being boys and girls...
‎To me... You're just Miki.
‎What does that mean?
‎Of course I'm me! I'm not "not" me.
‎I'm glad it was only light things inside.
‎Right. Are you okay from the fall?
‎Your head good? Your back?
‎I'm completely fine.
‎What happened just now?
‎It's like...
‎Come here.
‎No, wait...
‎No way, no way...
‎But... Me?
‎He can't possibly see me that way, right?
‎SWOOSH
‎Well then...
‎There. All done!
‎Leaving! Locking the doors!
‎I'll handle the keys!
‎Buh-bye. See you!
‎So quick.
‎Miki...
‎If Yota really feels that way...
‎how long has he felt it?
‎CLICK CLICK
‎WHOOSH WHOOSH
‎I thought we were just friends?
‎What do I do?
‎Has our friendship been so one-sided
‎all this time?
‎If it's all been a sham...
‎I love you.
‎Yeah.
‎I love you too.
‎What do I do?
‎All of our memories so far...
‎Everything he's said to me...
‎How nice he is to me...
‎This changes everything.
‎Subtitle translation by: Rychelle Brittain